broadwayworld.com 2019-12-04

# BroadwayWorld Privacy Policy

******  
We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed[here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/broadwayworld.com).  
**   
BroadwayWorld.com does not disclose your registration information to outside parties. We only release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our [Terms and Conditions of Use](https://www.broadwayworld.com/board/guide.cfm) and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of BroadwayWorld.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. 

BroadwayWorld recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of your personal information, and we have prepared this Privacy Policy to provide you with important information about our privacy practices. This Privacy Policy applies when you use a website, mobile or tablet application, or other online service.

**Information We Collect**

We may collect personal information about our users in various ways. For example, we may collect information that you provide to us, information that we collect through your use of the Services, and information that we collect from publicly available sources or third parties. 

**Information You Provide to Us**

When you register or otherwise interact with the Services, you may be invited to provide personal information to enhance your experience on our site. For example, during account registration, we may ask for information such as your name, e-mail address, year of birth, gender, street address, job title and industry and related information. We may collect payment information, such as your credit card number and expiration date, where appropriate to process a financial transaction you have requested. 

We also collect information that you provide us when you comment on articles, participate in message boards, and submit images, photos, videos, or other content to the Services. We may ask you for additional information at other times, such as when you enter a contest or participate in a promotion, when you post an online ad, or when you order products from us or otherwise engage with the Services. 

****Information About Your Use of the Services-** In addition to the information you provide to us directly, we may collect information about your use of the Services. For example, we may collect: **

Device information- such as your hardware model, IP address, other unique device identifiers, operating system version, browser type and settings, such as language and available font settings, and settings of the device you use to access the Services.

Usage information- such as information about the Services you use, the time and duration of your use of the Services and other information about your interaction with content offered through a Service, and any information stored using cookies, mobile ad identifiers, and similar technologies that we have set on your device. For detailed information about our use of cookies, web beacons, and other technologies, see Online Tracking and Advertising.

Location information- such as your computer's IP address, your mobile device's GPS signal or information about nearby WiFi access points and cell towers that may be transmitted to us when you use certain Services. Information From Third-Party Sources. We may receive information about you from publicly and commercially available sources, as permitted by law, which we may combine with other information we receive from or about you. For example, we may receive information about you from a social media site if you connect to the Services through that site. 

Other Information We Collect. We also may collect other information about you, your device, or your use of the services in ways that we describe to you at the point of collection or otherwise with your consent. You may choose not to provide us with certain types of information, but doing so may affect your ability to use some of the Services.

**How We Use Information**

To Provide and Manage the Services You Request. This includes, for example, processing your subscription, sending you electronic newsletters, or enabling you to participate in the features provided by the Services. It also includes providing personalized content and recommendations to you, including by email. Through such features, we are able to bring you information and content tailored to your individual interests and needs. 

To Contact You. We may periodically contact you with offers and information about the Services and our affiliates, including in connection with your accounts, online surveys, legal notices, news stories, new features that you are entitled to access, and other important information. You may opt out of receiving commercial email messages from us by following the instructions contained in those email messages. 

To Deliver Targeted Advertising. We may use your information to facilitate the delivery of targeted ads, promotions, and offers to you, on behalf of ourselves and advertisers, on and off the Services. Please see Online Tracking and Advertising for further information about our and third parties' use of cookies, web beacons, mobile ad identifiers, and other tracking technologies to provide you relevant ads, as well as information about how to disable cookies and make other choices related to targeted advertising. 

Notwithstanding any other provision, we partner with third parties that collect information across various channels, including offline and online, for purposes of delivering more relevant advertising to you or your business. Our partners use this information to recognize you across different channels and platforms, including but not limited to, computers, mobile devices, and Smart TVs, over time for advertising, analytics, attribution, and reporting purposes. Your data may be transferred outside of the country from which it was originally collected. 

To Better Understand Our Readers and Users. The Services conduct research on our users' demographics, interests and behavior based on the information we collect. We do this to better understand and serve our users, and to improve our products and services.

To Protect the Rights of the Services and others. We may use your personal information as we believe is necessary or appropriate to protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of the Services, its employees or agents, or other users and to comply with applicable law. 

Consent. We may otherwise use your information with your consent or at your direction. 

Other Parties When Required by Law or As Necessary to Protect Our Users and Services. We may share your personal information as we believe is necessary or appropriate to protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of the Services, our employees or agents or users or to comply with applicable law or legal process, including responding to requests from public and government authorities. 

Third Parties that Provide Content, Advertising, or Functionality. When you use our Services, third parties may collect or receive certain information about you and/or your use of the Services (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, information about your interactions with advertisements and other content), including through the use of cookies, beacons, mobile ad identifiers, and similar technologies, in order to provide content, advertising, or functionality or to measure and analyze ad performance, on our Services or other websites or platforms. This information may be combined with information collected across different websites, online services, and other linked or associated devices. These third parties may use your information to improve their own services and consistent with their own privacy policies. 

Other Parties in Connection With a Corporate Transaction. We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event that we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets to a third party, such as in the event of a merger, acquisition, or in connection with a bankruptcy reorganization. 

Otherwise With Your Consent or At Your Direction. In addition to the sharing described in this Privacy Policy, we may share information about you with third parties whenever you consent to or direct such sharing. 

We also may share other information with third parties in a manner that does not identify particular users, including, for example, aggregated data about how users are using our Services. 

**Links to Third-Party Sites**

Our Services may link to third-party websites and services that are outside our control. We are not responsible for the security or privacy of any information collected by other websites or other services. You should exercise caution, and review the privacy statements applicable to the third-party websites and services you use. 

**How to Access or Update Your Information & Other Privacy Choices Available To You**

You may access or modify your BroadwayWorld.com account on the User settings page. This link will also allow you to update your subscriptions to electronic newsletters provided by the Services and to view your comment history. 

Email Promotions. You may opt out of receiving commercial email messages from us by following the instructions contained in those email messages. 

Targeted Advertising. You may choose whether to receive some forms of targeted advertising from many ad networks, audience segment providers, ad serving vendors, and other service providers by visiting websites operated by the Network Advertising Initiative and Digital Advertising Alliance . Please see Online Tracking and Advertising and visit our Ad Choices pages for further information about how to disable cookies and other choices that may be available to you with respect to certain types of targeted advertising. 

**Online Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, **[click here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)**. 

We may collect and share hashed or anonymized user data with third-parties. Third parties may set cookies on users' browsers and collect user data using cookies or other technologies for their own use and subject to their own privacy policies. Third parties may combine user data with data collected across the internet or from other sites. Third parties may collect hashed user data using cookies/similar technologies from emails/communications. **Want to opt-out?[click here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).**

**Contacting us and accessing your personal information** If you have any queries or comments about this Privacy & Cookies Policy please contact us at contact@broadwayworld.com: 

**If you wish to review or receive a copy of the personal information we hold about you, please write to us at:  
** Data Protection Officer  
Wisdom Digital Media  
1001 Avenue of the Americas  
New York, NY 10018  
United States of America 

Thank you for making BroadwayWorld.com the web's premier theater resource and please let us know how we can serve you better!
